American Council for Polish Culture Collection. 1940-2013 CPAA 96-03
Connecticut Polish American Archives, Elihu Burritt Library, Central Connecticut State University, New Britain
- Inventory
  - ACPCC administrative correspondence., 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - ACPCC Administrative correspondence., 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - ACPCC Membership committee., 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - ACPCC Quarterly Review., 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - ACPCC Awards committee., 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - ACPCC Convention correspondence., 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - ACPCC Book collection committee., 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - ACPCC Constitution committee and review of Articles of Incorporation., 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - ACPCC 25th Anniversary Committee., 1971 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - ACPCC Credentials committee., 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - ACPCC Board meeting minutes and report., 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - ACPCC Convention, American University, reports., 1972 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - ACPCC Convention, American University, publicity., 1972 (Box 9, Folder 38A)
  - ACPCC Convention, American University, lecture by Victor Sawicki on Polish Theatre in the US., 1972 (Box 9, Folder 38B)
  - ACPCC Administrative correspondence., 1972 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - ACPCC Administrative correspondence, pt.1., 1973 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - ACPCC Administrative correspondence, pt.2., 1973 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - ACPCC Credentials committee., 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - ACPCC Convention committee correspondence., 1973 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - ACPCC Secretary's correspondence., 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - ACPCC President's notes and board meeting minutes., 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - ACPCC History book project - correspondence., 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - ACPCC President's correspondence., 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - ACPCC Board meeting minutes and reports., 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - ACPCC list of deceased members., 1973 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - ACPCC Convention, Villanova University - reports, minutes., 1973 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - ACPCC Convention, Villanova University - publicity., 1973 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - ACPCC Copernicus Society of Philadelphia - clippings., 1973 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - ACPCC National Shrine of Our Lady of Czestochowa - information pocket., 1973 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - ACPCC Convention, Alliance College, "Quo Vadis Polonia" lecture by Jerzy Brown., 1974 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - ACPCC Convention, Alliance College, minutes and reports., 1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - ACPCC Convention, Alliance College, general information., 1974 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - ACPCC Administrative correspondence, pt.1., 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - ACPCC Administrative correspondence, pt.2., 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - ACPCC Administrative correspondence, pt.3., 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - ACPCC Credential committee., 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - ACPCC Secretary's correspondence., 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - ACPCC legal matters., 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - ACPCC Board meeting minutes and reports., 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - ACPCC Convention committee correspondence., 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - ACPCC President's correspondence., 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - ACPCC information from anti-defamation committee of the Polish American Congress., 1973 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - ACPCC Friends of Polish Art - pamphlets., 1974-1978 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - ACPCC Youth committee., 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - ACPCC Bicentennial poster contest., 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - ACPCC Membership committee., 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - ACPCC Music committee correspondence., 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - ACPCC Ethnic Heritage., 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - ACPCC Awards committee., 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - ACPCC Kosciuszko Foundation correspondence., 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - ACPCC Smithsonian Institute correspondence., 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - ACPCC Board meetings minutes and reports., 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - ACPCC Bicentennial committee correspondence., 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - ACPCC Convention, Miami, information folder., 1975 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - ACPCC Convention, Miami, reports., 1975 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - ACPCC Convention, Miami, ballots and related material., 1975 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - ACPCC Administrative correspondence., August-October 1976 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - ACPCC Administrative correspondence., November 1976-January 1977 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - ACPCC Administrative Correspondence., February-April 1977 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - ACPCC Membership administrative correspondence., July 1976-March 1977 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - ACPCC Correspondence, brochures, clippings., 1976 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - ACPCC Membership correspondence., 1977 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - ACPCC Board meeting minutes., 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - ACPCC Convention, Chicago - club reports, correspondence, publicity., 1977 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - ACPCC President's administrative correspondence., August-December 1977 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - ACPCC Literary committee., 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - ACPCC Constitution committee., 1977 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - ACPCC Public relations., 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - ACPCC Community involvement., 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - ACPCC Cultural exchange., 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - ACPCC Convention, DePaul University, correspondence., August 1977 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - ACPCC Administrative correspondence., May-July 1977 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - ACPCC President's administrative correspondence., January-March 1978 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - ACPCC President's administrative correspondence., March-July 1978 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - ACPCC Correspondence, 20th Century Fund, Polish Heritage and scholarship., 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - ACPCC Correspondence, related to Kosciuszko plaque in Krakow., 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - ACPCC Polonia leadership committee., 1978 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - ACPCC Cultural exchange committee., 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - ACPCC Correspondence on lecture series., 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - ACPCC Community involvement., 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - ACPCC Correspondence related to the National Cultural Project., 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - ACPCC Book promotion committee., 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - ACPCC Convention, Orchard Lake, correspondence., 1978 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - ACPCC Awards Committee correspondence., 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - ACPCC Polish Arts Club of Chicago, various pamphlets., 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - ACPCC Board meetings minutes., 1977 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - ACPCC Board meetings minutes., 1978 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - ACPCC Membership committee report., 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - ACPCC Membership correspondence, A-L., 1977 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - ACPCC Membership correspondence, M-Z., 1977 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - ACPCC Membership correspondence, A-L., 1978 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - ACPCC Convention, Orchard Lake, correspondence, reports., 1978 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - ACPCC Convention, Orchard Lake, information pocket., 1978 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - ACPCC Correspondence, reports., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - ACPCC President's correspondence., 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - ACPCC Pabis scholarship., 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - ACPCC Tax exemption information., 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - ACPCC Publicity., 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - ACPCC Polish folk dance festival., 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - ACPCC Warsaw Autumn tour, program., 1978 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - ACPCC President's newsletter., 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - ACPCC Correspondence., 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - ACPCC National Youth conference, correspondence, program, list of participants., 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - ACPCC Membership correspondence, part 1., 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - ACPCC Membership correspondence, part 2., 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - ACPCC National Leadership Conference, correspondence., 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - ACPCC Executive board meetings, minutes., 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - ACPCC Folk dance festival., 1978 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - ACPCC Polish Folk Dance and Costume book., 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - ACPCC Treasurer's correspondence., 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - ACPCC Convention, Milwaukee - minutes., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - ACPCC Convention, Milwaukee - ballots., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - ACPCC Convention, Milwaukee - souvenir program and other brochures., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - ACPCC Convention, Milwaukee - program, reports, notes., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - ACPCC Regional discussion, meetings, publicity., 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - ACPCC Executive board meetings minutes., 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - ACPCC Administrative correspondence., 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - ACPCC President's newsletters., 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - ACPCC Awards committee correspondence., 1980 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - ACPCC Membership correspondence., 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - ACPCC President's correspondence., 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - ACPCC American Youth of Polish Descent (AYPD) Conference, San Antonio, program, reports., 1980 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - ACPCC Convention, San Antonio - pre convention correspondence., 1980 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - ACPCC Convention, San Antonio - programs of related events., 1980 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - ACPCC Convention, San Antonio - reports, minutes., 1980 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - ACPCC Convention, San Antonio - ballots., 1980 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - ACPCC Convention committee correspondence., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - ACPCC Correspondence., 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - ACPCC Convention, St. Louis - minutes, reports, list of participants., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - ACPCC Convention, St. Louis - publicity., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - ACPCC Convention, St. Louis - programs of related events, proclamations., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - ACPCC Post-convention correspondence., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - ACPCC AYPD Conference, Baltimore - program, newsletter, correspondence., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - ACPCC Poletown controversy - correspondence, press releases, clippings., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - ACPCC AYPD circulars and bulletins., 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - ACPCC Cultural exchanges and scholarships., 1975-1977 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - ACPCC Cultural exchanges and scholarships., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - ACPCC Board meeting, reports, notes., 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - ACPCC Administrative correspondence., 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - ACPCC Awards committee, correspondence, pamphlets., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - ACPCC AYPD 3rd conference, Chicago, Ill., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - ACPCC Awards committee chairman., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - ACPCC President's speeches (Anna Chrypinski)., 1978-1981 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - ACPCC Awards criteria., 1972-1981 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - ACPCC Board meetings., 1982 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - ACPCC Correspondence, notes, brochures., July 1981-August 1982 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - ACPCC Correspondence, related to book sale., 1982 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - ACPCC Convention, Chicago - publicity, financial report, annual report., 1982 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - ACPCC Membership committee correspondence., 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - ACPCC President's correspondence., 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - ACPCC Vice President's correspondence., 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - ACPCC Board meetings, minutes., 1983 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - ACPCC Convention, Baltimore - convention guidelines., 1983 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - ACPCC Convention, Baltimore - correspondence, agenda, publicity., 1983 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - ACPCC American Youth of Polish Descent (AYPD) 4th Annual Conference, Washington D.C., agenda., 1983 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - ACPCC Administrative correspondence., 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - ACPCC Membership committee., 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - ACPCC Board meetings minutes., 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - ACPCC Convention, Washington DC - minutes, annual report., 1984 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - ACPCC Executive Board meeting, Orlando, Fl., March 1985 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - ACPCC Membership committee., 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - ACPCC Affiliate The American Institute of Polish Culture - information pocket., 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - ACPCC Convention, Buffalo - program, list of affiliated members, list of officers., 1985 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - ACPCC Convention, Buffalo - committee reports., 1985 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - ACPCC Convention, Buffalo - publicity, news., 1985 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - ACPCC Board meetings minutes., 1985 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - ACPCC Convention, Alliance College - agenda, programs., 1985 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - ACPCC YAPD 4th Conference, Orchard Lake - agenda., 1986 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - ACPCC Convention, Ypsilanti, Michigan - agenda, program, keynote speech., 1987 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - ACPCC Convention Ypsilanti, Michigan - publicity., 1987 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - ACPCC Membership committee., 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - ACPCC Convention, Hartford - souvenir program, minutes., 1988 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - ACPCC Convention, Hartford - minutes, programs., 1988 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - ACPCC Dues changes., 1988 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - ACPCC Constitution amendment, name change from American Council of Polish Cultural Clubs ACPCC to ACPC., 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - ACPCC membership committee., 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - ACPCC Dues changes., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - ACPCC Administrative correspondence., 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - ACPCC Membership committee., 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - ACPCC Board meetings., 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - ACPCC 41st Convention, Philadelphia - program, anniversary pamphlet., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - ACPC Convention, Philadelphia - minutes, program, reports., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - ACPC Convention, publicity., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - ACPC Roster of all members and subscribers., 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - ACPC Norwid Memorial Committee correspondence., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - ACPC Constituion and by-laws and nomination guidelines, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - ACPC report from the Mission Trip to Poland, photos, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - ACPC - correspondence, minutes, resolutions, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - ACPC - minutes, president reports, press releases, financial information, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - ACPC - correspondence, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - ACPC - correspondence, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - ACPC - minutes, meetings, press re;leases, reports, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - ACPC clippings, programs, events calendar, photos, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - ACPC - grant application "Community based computer centers in Poland", 1992 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - ACPC - correspondence, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - ACPC - minutes, reports, announcements, financial information, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - ACPC - Congressman Alvin O'Konski, biographical information, clippings, 1945-1957 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - ACPC Affiliate Resources Committee - correspondence, reports and related material., 1993-1997 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - ACPC Affiliate Resources Committee - Polish American Heritage Pocket, publication by Yonkers Public Schools., 1993 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - ACPC Affiliate Resources Committee - survey of affiliated members., 1994 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - ACPC Affiliate Resources Committee - survey on contacts with institutions of higher education., 1995 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - ACPC affiliate The Polish Arts Club of Trenton, NJ - promotional material on Poland., 1997 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - ACPC initiative to promote May 3rd Constitution and Polish cultural events., 1996 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - ACPC "Poland Traveling Trunk" introduction to presentation., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - ACPC "Poland Traveling Trunk" content, registry, list of resources., 1987-1997 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - ACPC 47th Annual Convention, Las Vegas - 2 VHS tapes., 1995 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - ACPC Sembrich Opera Museum, Ronald Pesha production (VHS tape)., 19 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - ACPCC Newsletters and bulletins (scattered issues)., 1963-11967 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Polish Heritage - correspondence., 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 1A)
  - Polish Heritage supporting material, v.32, no.1., 1981 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Polish Heritage supporting material, v.32, no.2., 1981 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Polish Heritage supporting material, v.32, no.4., 1981 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Polish Heritage supporting material, v.33, no.1., 1982 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Polish Heritage club news, v.33, no.2., 1982 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Polish Heritage supporting material, v.33, no.2., 1982 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Polish Heritage supporting material, v.33, no.3., 1982 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Polish Heritage clubs news, v.33, no.3., 1982 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Polish Heritage supporting material, v.33, no.4., 1982 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Polish Heritage club news, v.33, no.4., 1982 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Polish Heritage supporting material, v.34, no.1., 1983 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Polish Heritage clubs news, v.34, no.1., 1983 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Polish Heritage supporting material, v.34, no.2., 1983 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Polish Heritage clubs news, v.34, no.2., 1983 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Polish Heritage supporting material, v.34, no.3., 1983 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Polish Heritage club news, v.34, no.3., 1983 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Polish Heritage supporting material, v.34, no.4., 1983 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Polish Heritage club news, v.34, no.4., 1983 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Polish Heritage supporting material, v.35, no.1., 1984 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Polish Heritage club news, v.35, no.1., 1984 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Polish Heritage supporting material, v.35, no.2., 1984 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Polish Heritage club news, v.35, no.2., 1984 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Polish Heritage supporting material, v.35, no.3., 1984 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Polish Heritage club news, v.35, no.3., 1984 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - ACPC - official publications for annual conventions., 1949-2005 (Box 15)
  - ACPC - IRS form 990EZ, 1991-1995 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - ACPC - Treasurer's correspondence, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - ACPC - Financial reports, work sheets, drafts of 1993 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - ACPC - Treasurer's correspondence, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - ACPC - Convention Committee Financial Records 94-95, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - ACPC Finanical Reports, Work sheets, drafts of 1994- (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - ACPC - Financial Reports Jan, 1994- Dec, 1999, 1994-1999 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - ACPC - Treasurer's Correspondence Part I, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - ACPC - Treasurer's Correspondence part II, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - ACPC - Worksheets, Drafts, Financial Reports of 1995 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - ACPC - Cidrich, Mahalak Audit Report, 1995-1997 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - ACPC - Treasurer's Correspondence Part I, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - ACPC - Treasurer's Correspondence Part II, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - ACPC - National Combined Federal Application Copy, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - ACPC - 1996 Tax Return Notes (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - ACPC - 1996 IRS Return, Form 990 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - ACPC - Search for CPA Firm, 1996-1998 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - ACPC - A.C.P.C. Audit Reports, 1996-1999 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - ACPC - Treasurer's Correspondence, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - ACPC - 1997 IRS Return Form 990 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - ACPC - National Combined Federal Campaign Application, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - ACPC - Treasurer's Correspondence, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - ACPC - Treasurer's Correspondence Part II, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - ACPC - Materials for 98' Grant Request, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - ACPC - National Combined Federal Campaign Application Copy, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - ACPC - 1998 IRS Return Form 990 (Box 16, Folder 25A)
  - ACPC - Treasurer's Correspondence Part I, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - ACPC - Treasurer's Correspondence part II, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - ACPC - Closed CD's Franklin Bank, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - ACPC - National Council for the Social Studies Exhibit, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - ACPC - 1999 IRS Return, Form 990 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - ACPC - Correspondence with IRS, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - ACPC - National Combined Federal Campaign Application Copy, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - ACPC - Royal Alliance account, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - ACPC - 2000 IRS Return, Form 990 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - ACPC - Financial Statements, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - ACPC - Financial Statements + Donations Jan-March, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - ACPC - Financial Statements + Donations April-June, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - ACPC - Financial Statements + Donations July- September, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - ACPC - Financial Statements + Donations October- December, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - ACPC - Financial Statements + Donations pt. I, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - ACPC - Financial Statements + Donations pt. II, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - ACPC - Financial Statements + Invoices pt. I, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - ACPC - Financial Statements + Invoices pt. II, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - ACPC - Journal Accounts + Tax Books, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - ACPC - Bank Statements, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - ACPC - Financial Statements + Donations pt. I, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - ACPC - Financial Statements + Donations pt. II, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - ACPC - Financial Statements + Donations pt. II, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - ACPC - Financial Statements + Invoices pt. I, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - ACPC - Financial Statements + Invoices pt. II, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - ACPC - Bank Statements pt. I, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - ACPC - Bank Statements pt. II, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - ACPC - Journal Accounts + Tax Books, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - ACPC - Bank Statements, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - ACPC - Journal Accounts + Tax Books pt. I, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - ACPC - Journal Accounts and Tax Books pt. II, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - ACPC - Financial Statements + Invoices pt. I, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - ACPC - Financial Statements + Invoices pt. II, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - ACPC - Financial Statements + invoices pt. III, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - ACPC - Financial Statements + Donations pt. I, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - ACPC - Financial Statements + Donations pt. II, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - ACPC - Financial Statements + Donations pt. III, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - ACPC - Financial Statements + Donations pt. IV, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - ACPC - CD Certificate Deposit Slips + Money Market Accounts, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - ACPC - Accounting Books for Special Events, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - ACPC - General financial journal, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - ACPC - Raymond James Associates - financial statements, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - ACPC - Financial Statements, Invoices pt. I, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - ACPC - Financial Statements, Invoices pt. II, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - ACPC - Emails pt. I, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - ACPC - Emails pt. II, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - ACPC - Emails pt. III, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - ACPC - Emails pt. I, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - ACPC - Emails pt. II, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - ACPC - Emails, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - ACPC - Emails, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - ACPC - Programs, Events, Related Clippings, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - ACPC - President's Newsletter, 1996-1999 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - ACPC - Background History of the A.C.P.C (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - ACPC - Constitution, 1990-1995 (Box 18, Folder 4)